本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版
同志们  好消息啊
Guys. Great news!
我觉着我已经想好去哪开我的生日派对了
I think I know where I want to have my birthday party.
你的生日派对  不是在六个月前吗
Your birthday party? Your birthday was six months ago.
没错  但是因为我生病而把派对取消了  还记得吗
Yeah. But my party was cancelled because I got sick, remember?
然后又因为我捅了个篓子  导致派对再次取消
And then it was cancalled because I was bad.
紧接着又离圣诞节太近了  派对这事又搁浅了
And it was too close to Christmas and then I was banned again.
看来咱们还真没为他开过派对
I guess we never did have a party for him.
那咱么就给他开一个
Well I suppose we could have one for him now.
我是说咱们从没有过偏心  对吧
I mean we do love him as much as the other kids, right?
噢
Oh...
这个嘛
Well...
我决定在轰隆地带开派对
The party is gonna be at The Boom Zone.
-给你  了解下  -轰隆地带
-Here. Take a look. -Boom zone.
绝对是个好地方
It's totally fun.
是与我十个好朋友开生日派对的绝佳地点
And it's the perfect birthday party place for me and ten of my closet friends.
我更喜欢称那十个好朋友为  圣诞老人
Or as I like to call them: gift bringers.
哇啊  花费还不少呢
Wow. That's gonna run us some money.
不如留着以后给那几个孩子办一个
I mean maybe for one of the other kids.
-盖比  我们如你所愿  -太好了
-Gabe, we'll do it. -Yes!
说得太好了
Now you're talking.
-答应我们一个条件  -还有条件啊
-On one condition. -Oh and you're still talking.
如果你能在一周内不惹事生非  我们就给你开派对
We can have a party at the Boom Zone if you can be good for a whole week.
小事一桩
I can do that.
别给你哥和你姐找麻烦
Can't be mean to your brother and sisters?
-没问题  -不能取笑我的厨艺
-No problem. -Can't make fun of my cooking?
虽然困难  但是也没问题
Harder but I can do that.
同样不能取笑你爸的体重
And you can't make fun of your father's weight.
吼  吼  永别了轰隆地带
Ho ho. Bye bye Boom Zone.
老爸  你太小看我了  我可以做到的
No dad. Dad, you're wrong. I can do this.
在接下来的一周内  对于你的体重我闭口不谈
For the next week, I will not say anything about your weight.
-真的  -真的
-Really? -Yeah.
-那就祝你好运了  -谢了  大秃头
-Good luck with that. -Thanks, baldie.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  sarina
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第十一集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E11  Gabes 12.5 Birthday
-不嘛  你来告诉她  -不  你来说
-No, you tell her. -No, you.
-不  你说  -不  不  你来告诉她
-No, you. -No no, you tell her.
有完没完
Somebody!
是这样的  德里克说了句至理名言
Okay, so Derek said the deepest thing.
-告诉她吧  宝贝  -今早上我盯着碗里的麦片粥
-Tell her, sweetie. -I was looking at my cereal this morning.
然后我就在想  哇  世上没有完全一样的麦片
And I was thinking... wow... no two flakes are exactly alike.
原话是雪花  而不是麦片
That's snowflakes, not cornflakes.
我还写了一首关于它的诗
I actually wrote a poem about it.
如果你想听  我会在下次诗歌交流会上朗诵的
If you wanna hear it, I will be reading my next poetry slam.
-我们会去听的  -呃  其实
-We'll be there. -Um, actually,
那天晚上俺还有别的交流会要去
I got another slam to go to that night.
德里克并没有说是哪天晚上
Derek didn't say what night it was.
俺整周都有交流会
I got slams all week.
俺是交流会达人
I'm just slammed.
-我们会去的  -好的
-We'll be there. -Cool.
那我走了
I gotta go.
知道吗  宝贝  如果你起床后想读点什么
You know, babe, if you wanna get up and read something,
-读首诗是个很好的选择  -知道了
-That would be awesome. -Okay.
很好  今晚的主题是痛苦
Cool. The theme of the night is pain.
了解
Okay.
-再见了  -再见
-See ya. -Okay.
你要写一首诗
<i>You're gonna write a poem</i>
关于痛苦的  然后起床后去读它
About pain then get up and read it?
我才不会写呢
I don't think so.
但你刚刚答应他了
You just said you would.
-是吗  -是的
-I did? -Yes.
-就在他把胳膊搭在你肩膀上时  -该死
-When he put his arm on your shoulder. -Oh darn.
每当他那样时  我就不能思考了
Whenever he does that I can't think straight.
是吗  那你真的喜欢
Uh-huh. So did you really like.
-他说的麦片粥的事吗  -麦片粥什么事啊
-That thing he said about cereal? -What did he say about cereal?
嘿  亲爱的  裤子太紧了
Hey, honey, these pants are too tight.
我新买的大号裤子放哪了
Where are the new bigger ones I bought?
你穿的就是大号的
Those are the new bigger ones.
我先离开下吧  这种环境太容易诱使我犯错了
I'm leaving. This is not a safe environment for me.
裤子也不是太紧
These pants aren't so tight.
这招应该会管用的
I can make this work.
好了  亲爱的
Okay, Bob honey,
我是如此的深爱着你
I love you to pieces, my dear,
但你的腰围已经成为孩子们的安全隐患了
But your waistline has now become a safety issue for the children.
亲爱的  我很是乐意去减下几磅肉
Honey, I would love to lose a couple of pounds,
但是食疗对我不起作用啊
But diets just don't seem to work for me.
老爸  这跟食疗...
Well, dad, it's not just abo...
老爸  这跟食疗没关系
Dad, it's not about dieting.
你所需要的就是健康饮食配合适量的运动
What you need is healthier eating choices combined with exercise.
-什么意思  -少吃培根  多做运动
-What is that supposed to mean? -Less bacon, more shakin'.
我可以帮你  做你的训练师
I can help you out, be like your trainer.
好的
Okay.
非常感谢  但我不需要你帮忙
Thank you very much, but I don't need your help.
这下好了  内裤也撕了
Yup, split the underwear too.
明早开始
Get started in the morning?
呃  泰迪  你没事吧
Uh, Teddy, are you okay?
有事  我的麦片粥不和我说话了
No, my cereal's not speaking to me.
难道你的麦片粥以前和你说过话吗
Has your cereal spoken to you before?
没有  我只是  我需要一些灵感
No, I just... I need some inspiration.
我和德里克说我周六晚上
I told Derek that I'd read an original poem.
读过一篇原创诗歌  但目前为止  毫无思路
On Saturday night and so far I've got nothing.
你是说诗歌吗
Poetry you say?
我曾经告诉过你  我也写过诗吗
Have I ever mentioned that I write poetry?
老妈  请不要掺和这件事
Mom, please don't make this about you.
好吧  那样就太自私了
Of course, that would be selfish.
噢  我曾经写过一首关于自私的好诗
Ooh! I wrote a great poem about selfishness.
好像是这样写的“我  我  我  我”...
It goes like this: "me me me me"...
老妈
Mom!
抱歉
Sorry.
说说看你要写的诗的主题是什么
Okay, what is your poem supposed to be about?
这个  应该是关于痛苦的
Well, it's supposed to be about pain,
但我想不出任何痛苦的事情
But I can't think about anything painful.
我有个相亲相爱的家庭
I have happily-married parents,
有房有车  衣食无忧
A roof over my head, food on my table.
你们为什么给我一个这么完美的生活
Why'd you guys have to give me such a good life?
啊
Ah.
-一切就绪  -好的
-All right! -Okay.
-开始吧  -看起来不错嘛  老爸
-Let's go! -Looking good, dad.
首先  要感谢你没有穿背心
For starters, thank you for not wearing a tank top.
好了  我们先做什么
All right, what do we do first?
先做...桑巴运动
We... Sambacise.
-什么东西  -是一种名人想出来的东西
-<i>Wh</i>is this? -This is a celebrity workout program.
将桑巴舞与运动相结合
Which combines exercise with samba dancing.
噢  我才不管呢  这东西会不会让我显得很白痴
Oh, I don't know. This isn't gonna make me look stupid, is it?
看来答案很明显
<i>Well, that's a big yes.</i>
别这样啊  老爸  试试看嘛
Come on, dad, just give it a chance.
你看贝蒂·怀特跳得有多开心
Look how much fun Betty white's having.
（注：贝蒂·怀特，美国资深老演员）
哇  那位老太太还真是无处不在啊
Wow, that woman is everywhere.
-跟我跳  -好吧
-Just follow me. -Uh-huh.
-注意侧步  -哇啊
-To the side. -Whoa!
-很好  注意这部分...哇  -噢  快瞧瞧
-Yeah, and watch this part... wha! -Oh! Look at that!
很好  继续  老爸  非常好  非常好
Yeah, keep going, dad. There you go, there you go.
嘿  等一下  贝蒂怎么有支玫瑰
Hey, wait a minute. Betty's got a rose.
我早就准备好了  老爸
Well, way ahead of you, dad.
-谢谢  先生  -不客气
-Thank you, sir. -Uh-huh.
好了  咱们继续
All right, here we go.
耶
Yeah!
不赖啊
Ain't bad.
想什么呢
Anything on your mind?
我可以取笑这件事吗
I can make fun of this, right?
这件事和你的体重并不相关
I mean, this doesn't have anything to do with your weight.
噢  还真有关系
Oh, yes it does.
因为我正在燃烧卡路里
I'm doing this to <i>lo</i>weight.
大鹏展翅
Big finish.
啊
Ah!
“深深地  揪心的痛”
"deep, gut-wrenching pain,"
就像是一头野兽从里到外慢慢吞噬着我
Like an animal devouring me from the inside out
我声嘶力竭的哭泣
I cried in agony.
“最后变成了野兽”
"Then gave into the beast."
谢谢  诗的题目是“麦片粥”
Thank you. That was called "cereal."
-好了  该你上了  -好的
-Okay, you're up. -Okay.
好的
Okay.
大家好  大家好
Hello. Hello.
嗨  我是泰迪·邓肯
Hi. I'm Teddy Duncan.
我的诗叫做“流鼻血”
And this is called "nosebleed."
“血啊  血啊  看你肆意狂流”
"blood blood, watch it flow,"
从我的鼻子往外流
From my nose it did go,
我尖叫着  我哭泣着
I was a screamer, I was a crier,
医生拿了个加湿器
The doctor called for a humidifier,
曾试着用冰块  曾试着用棉花
We tried ice, we tried cotton,
我仰起头...
I put my head way back...
“不流了”
"Nuttin'."
谢谢
Thank you.
这诗真的有那么垃圾吗
Was it really as bad as I thought?
没有
No.
没有  当然没有  只是
No no, it was...
只是  噢  呃
It wa... oh, uh,
-我去接电话了  -噢
-I gotta take this. -Oh.
您好
Hello.
厉害  假电话  真的有那么糟糕吗
Okay, fake phone call... was it really that bad?
等一下  您好
Hang on. Hello?
嘿  少玩这套
Hey! Stop that.
真不敢相信我居然
I can't believe I just made.
让自己在德里克面前像个傻子
A complete fool of myself in front of Derek.
那又如何  谁在乎德里克怎么想的
So? Who cares what Derek thinks?
我在乎  他可是我的男朋友
I do. He's my boyfriend.
听着  他现在看起来是不错
Look, he's fine for now,
但他决不会一直这样下去
But he isn't exactly a keeper, right?
-此话怎讲  -没看出来吗  你俩不是一类人
-What do you mean? -Come on. You guys are so different.
是吗  怎么不是一类人了
Well... different? How are we different?
你聪明伶俐  他是德里克
You're smart. He's Derek.
你妙趣横生  他是德里克
You're fun. He's Derek.
你兴趣盎然  他是德里克
You're interesting. He's Derek.
你讨厌德里克吗
So you don't like Derek?
好吧  也许我也讨厌你的男朋友
Okay. Well, maybe I don't like your boyfriend.
我的雷雷哪里不好了
And what is wrong with my ray-ray?
首先  你叫他雷雷就让我很不爽
Well, the fact that you call him ray-ray for starters.
“雷雷说这个  雷雷说那个”
"ray-ray said this. Ray-ray said that."
有时候我只能求求
Sometimes I just pray-pray.
你不要再喊雷雷了
You'll shut up about ray-ray.
好吧  你的求求成真了
Well, your prayers have just been answered,
因为我不会再和你说话了
Because I'm never talking to you again.
是吗  那敢情好啊
Well, that... that's right!
去跑跑到你的雷雷身旁旁吧
Go run-run away-way to ray-ray!
听着  打住  这不是一首诗
Look... no, it's not a poem.
但你们喜欢吗
But you liked it?
哇  外面的雪下的还真大啊
Whoa, it is really coming down out there.
好了  老妈  虽然这一路走下来并不容易
Well, mom, it wasn't easy,
但我最终挺下来这一整周了
But I've been good for an entire week.
轰隆地带  我来也
Boom zone, here I come!
我不得不说  盖比  你的努力让老天都哭了
I have to say, Gabe, you have really earned this party.
没错  给你
Hmm. Here you go.
-什么东西  -是一张讽刺清单
-What's this? -It's a list of bad things
把那些想说但说不成的  我都记下来了
I thought of saying but didn't.
第一部分是关于老爸肥胖的笑话
Part one is fat jokes about dad.
盖比  这并不好...
Gabe, there's nothing funny about...
这个太好笑了
That one's pretty good.
对于那个我很得意
I like that one.
噢  那个更好笑了
Oh, that one's even better.
那一个
That one...
怎么了  笑什么呢
What? What's so funny?
没什么
Nothing.
噢  有蛋糕
Ooh! Cake.
“亲爱的老爸  坚强点”
"dear dad, be strong."
不要吃这蛋糕
Do not eat this cake.
“爱你  你的儿子以及训练师PJ”
"Love, your son and trainer P.J."
“亲爱的老爸
"dear dad,
看来你把我留给你的第一张纸条扔了”
so you've thrown away my first note."
我现在给你第二次机会做出正确的决定
Here is a second chance to make the right decision.
“相信你的  你的儿子  PJ”
"Your son who believes in you, P.J."
“亲爱的老爸
"dear dad,
好吧  看来纸条对你没用”
Okay, so notes aren't your thing."
-嗨  温茨夫人  -嘿  泰迪  快进来
-Hi, Mrs. Wentz. -Hey. Goodness, Teddy, get in here.
哇  外面的雪真不小
Oh wow, it's really snowing out there.
我快无法在您的车道上停车了
I could barely park in your driveway.
我们没有车道啊
We don't have a driveway.
好吧  至少我知道它能去哪了
Okay. Well, I know where it <i>could</i> go.
能和艾薇谈谈吗
Can I talk to Ivy?
我们昨天吵了一架  我想向她道歉
We got in a fight last night and I really need to apologize.
噢  抱歉  泰迪  艾薇不在家
Oh, I'm sorry, Teddy. Ivy's not here.
她去你家了  她说她要向你道歉
She went to your house because she said she needed to apologize to you.
-是吗  -是的
-She did? -Mm-hmm.
好吧  我  我最好还是先回家吧
Okay, well, I... I'd better go home then.
噢算了  泰迪  你哪也别去了
Oh no, Teddy, you're not going anywhere.
嗨  温茨先生
Hi, Mr. Wentz.
过来  看看这个
Come on, take a look at this.
-好吧  -现在正如你所看见的
-Okay. -Now as you can see,
落基山脉上方的高压系统长期不退
We've got a high-pressure system stalled over the Rockies,
高压系统从加拿大带来了来自北极的冷空气
And it's pushing cold arctic air down from Canada.
导致了这里疯狂的春季降雪
Giving us a freak spring blizzard.
-噢  -哈里总想成为一名气象员
-Oh. -Harry always wanted to be a weatherman,
但是他接受了管道用品工作
But he answered the call of plumbing supplies.
知道了  最新消息
Mmm. Breaking news.
他们刚刚封闭了所有路段
They've just closed all the roads,
而这对于你这位年轻的女士意味着
And that means that you, young lady,
你只能乖乖的呆在这里了  也许是一整晚
Are gonna be staying right here, maybe overnight.
什么  抱歉  我不能呆一整晚
What? I'm sorry, I can't stay overnight.
我还想祝贺一下阿布纳·约翰逊
I'd like to also send a shout out to Abner Johnson.
今天是他的104岁生日
He's 104 today.
他在和谁说话呢
Who is he talking to?
没谁  哈里
Nobody. Harry
你知道你没有在电视中  对吧
You do know that you're not really on tv, right?
我当然知道了  现在话筒转交给你  玛丽
Of course I do. Back to you, Mary lo...
我们估计今天的降雪量将达到两英尺
<i>We're expecting up to</i> <i>two feet of snow today,</i>
请大家呆在家中  不要外出
<i>So stay in your homes</i> <i>and off the roads.</i>
艾薇  快进来
Ivy? Get in here.
你怎么来了
What are you doing here?
我来是想向泰迪道歉
I came over to apologize to Teddy.
泰迪去你家给你道歉去了
Teddy went to your house to apologize to you.
-什么  -现在所有道路都关闭了
-What? -And now the roads are all closed,
看来你要困在这里一阵子了
So you're gonna be stuck here awhile.
真的  你是说一整晚吗
Really? You mean overnight?
几天也可以啊
Even maybe a few days?
-太好了  -啊  出发了  大家
-Yes! -Ah. Let's go, people.
我们要去参加派对了
We've got a party to go to.
亲爱的盖比  恐怕要告诉你一些噩耗
Gabe honey, I'm afraid we have some bad news.
在去往轰隆地带的路上告诉我也成啊
Just tell me on the way to the boom zone.
不成  过来和我坐下
No no. Come sit with mama, okay?
好吧
Okay.
如今  宝贝  由于暴风雪
Now, sweetie, because of the blizzard,
我们大家不能开车去任何地方了
Nobody's able to drive anywhere and...
我恐怕你的派对也泡汤了
I'm afraid your party is off.
搞什么  又来
What?! Again?!
-想开点  深呼吸  -难以置信
-No no, take a deep breath. -I can't believe this!
我白当一个星期的哑巴了吗
I've been keeping my mouth shut for nothing?!
-好了  盖比  冷静下  -省省吧  胖墩儿
-Okay, Gabe, just calm... -Save it, tubby!
-嘿  盖比  -你的厨艺烂到家了  你就一白痴
-Hey, Gabe! -Your cooking stinks! And you're stupid!
-我什么也没说啊  -没错  但你在想一些白痴的事情
-I didn't say anything. -Yeah, but you were thinking something stupid.
我讨厌我的生活
I hate my life!
天啊  这比我家好多了
Man. This is so much better than my house.
你听着  泰迪  大多数人们认为
You see, Teddy, most people actually think.
当温度升高时
That when the temperature rises,
同时也伴随着大气压的升高
So does the barometric pressure...
但事实并非如此
But that is not the case.
哈里  别烦那个小女孩了
Harry, leave that girl alone.
让我们做些能让泰迪高兴的事情  比如
Let's do something Teddy would enjoy, like...
智力拼图
A Jigsaw puzzle.
天啊
Oh!
-盖比  你还好吧  -别烦我
-Gabe, are you okay? -Leave me alone.
听着  宝贝  我了解你的感受
Look, babe, I know how you feel.
不  你不了解  你的生日从不缺少派对
No, you don't. You've <i>never</i> gone without a party on your birthday.
就好像已经有一百万次了
You've had like a million of them.
那好  那我就准备少一次派对
Okay, I'm gonna let that one go,
因为我知道你现在很是受伤
Because I know you're hurting right now.
但我向你保证  你会有生日派对的
But I promise you: You <i>are</i> going to have a birthday party.
是吗  当我百岁生日时
Yeah, when I'm 100.
老到我都无法吹灭蜡烛时吗
And I can't even blow out my candles?
好了  如果你非要提到爷爷的话
Okay, if you're referring to grandpa,
他才七十岁  何况他还有哮喘
He's only 70 and he has asthma.
泰迪  你怎么没有吃你的肝脏和洋葱啊
Teddy, you've hardly touched your liver and onions.
嗯
Mmm.
我要留着肝脏来吃早餐
I had liver for breakfast.
有什么需求吗
Got any requests?
来辆雪地汽车怎么样
How about a snowmobile?
来唱“小船摇啊摇”怎么样
How about "row row row your boat"?
我的最爱啊  来吧
It's my favorite. Come on.
其实  温茨先生  你真的不必
Actually, Mr. Wentz, you really don't have to...
划啊划  划啊划  划你的小船入河流
<i>Row row row your boat gently down the stream</i>
好开心  好开心  好开心  生活不过是一场梦
<i>Merrily merrily merrily merrily, life is but a dream. </i>
艾薇在家的时候我们可不敢这么唱  她不让
We can't do this when Ivy's home. She won't let us.
哈  我真的好怀念她
Ha. I miss her so much.
再来一遍
Rounds!
-噢  -划啊划  划啊划  划你的小船
-Oh! <i>-Row row row your boat...</i>
-泰迪  -划啊划  划啊划  划你的小船
-Teddy!<i> -Row row row your boat... </i>
划啊划  划啊划  划你的小船入河流
<i>Row row row your boat gently down the stream... </i>
不管是什么  但我敢肯定不怎么样
Whatever this is, I'm sure it's gonna be lame.
噢  我可不这么想  来吧  查莉
Oh, I don't think so. Hit it, Charlie.
生日快乐
Surprise!
Happy Birthday!
-搞什么  -“搞什么”
-What's all this? -"What's all this?"
搞的是邓肯欢乐地带
It's the Duncan fun zone!
既然我们去不成你的派对
Well, since we can't go to your party,
我们就把派对搬家里来了
We brought the party to you.
楼下注意喽
Look out below!
-噢  -噢
-Oh! -<i>Oh!</i>
-噢  -你想试试吗
-Oh! -You want a turn?
看来你被整的颓废了
You look kinda sick.
好耶  我当然要试试了
<i>Yeah.</i> <i>Of course I want a turn!</i>
好耶
All right!
划啊划  划啊划  划你的小船入河流
<i>Row row row your boat</i> <i>gently down the stream </i>
好开心  好开心  好开心  生活不过是一场梦
<i>Merrily merrily merrily merrily, life...</i>
等等  等等  大伙儿  这首歌有结尾吗
Wait wait. Guys guys, does this song have an ending?
如果有  那我们也从没有唱到过
If it does, we've never found it.
现在
Now...
德语版
In German!
呜  划啊划  划啊划  划啊划
Ooh! <i>Zeile zeile</i> <i>zeile irh boot </i>
划你的小船入河流
<i>Sanft den strom hinab!</i>
好开心  好开心  好开心
<i>Lustig lustig</i> <i>lustig lustig</i>
生活不过是一场梦
<i>leben ist</i> <i>nur ein traum!</i>
呃
<i>ugh!</i>
耶
Yeah!
噢
Ooh.
还有更多
<i>and many more...</i>
耶
Yeah!
-耶  -嘿
-Yay! -Hey!
谢谢大家
Thanks, everybody.
这绝对是史上最强的派对了
This really has been the best party ever.
听着  抱歉说你很胖
Look, I'm sorry I called you fat,
很白痴  厨艺很烂
Stupid and a bad cook.
我是说  即使你很胖  很白痴  厨艺很烂
I mean, even though you are fat, stupid and a bad cook...
我还是爱你们大家的
I love you all.
当然  我们也爱你
Well, we love you too.
当然不像爱其他孩子一样多
Not as much as the others, of course...
但是
<i>...But...</i>
-泰迪姐  -大家好
-Teddy! -Hey, everybody.
-嘿  -噢  嘿
-Hey! -Oh, hey.
你怎么回来的  道路不是全封闭了吗
What are you doing here? The roads are all closed.
-是啊  我走回来的  -为什么回来了
-Yeah, I walked. -Why did you do that?
我想我可以回答这个问题
I think I can answer that.
-肝脏和洋葱  -没错
-Liver and onions? -Yup.
-智力拼图  -是的
-Jigsaw puzzle? -Uh-huh.
-“小船摇啊摇”  -还是德语版的
-"row row row your boat"? -In German.
-来抱抱  -好的
-Come here. -Okay.
好了  查莉  暴风雪平息了
Well, Charlie, the storm's over,
太阳出来了  盖比有了个无与伦比的派对
Sun's shining, Gabe had a great party.
还有  噢  最劲爆的新闻
And... ooh, best of all,
多亏了桑巴运动  老爸瘦了两磅
Thanks to sambacising, dad's lost two pounds.
没错  他激动坏了  现在他开始学
Yeah, he was so excited, he's now graduated to...
探戈运动
Tangocise!
噢
Oh!
啊咿咿
Ay-yi-yi.
好运喽  查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
哼
Huh.
最终  就剩咱俩了
Finally, we are alone.
-想偷吃  -哇噢噢
-Nuh-uh-uh. -Whoa-ho-ho!
你怎么
How did you...
但这个  但  你怎么
But it was... but... how... how did you...
赶紧抓个苹果  回去睡觉
Now grab an apple and go back to bed.
-你只有个头是吗  -是的
-You're just a head, right?  -Yes
-没有胳膊  没有腿  -没有
-No arms, no legs? -Nope.
-只有眼睛  对吧  -当然
-Got eyes though, right? -Of course.
-那好  那你只能眼睁睁地看着我了  -不
-Well, then you can watch me. -<i>No. No no.</i>.
不  不  不
No no no no no!
现在我希望连眼睛都不要有
Now I'm wishing I didn't have eyes.
-希望你没有牙齿  -不要啊
-Wish you didn't have teeth? -No no!